Continuing Education Pamphlet Collection
Continuing Education Pamphlet Collection
- Alphabetical listing
  - Linking the National Voluntary Sector (Box 43)
  - Listen Real Loud-News of Women's Liberation Worldwide (Box 43)
  - Listing of Periodicals Received by Syracuse University (Box 78)
  - Literacy (Box 69)
    See also Adult Literacy Responses to Comic Strip Narratives Among Inmates of a Correctional Institution; Agencies, Organizations, and Sponsors of Civic Literacy; Business Council Effective Literacy; Illiteracy; International Literacy Year; Report of the Texas Literacy Council; Worldlit Newsletter of World Literacy of Canada
  - Literacy Documentation (Box 3)
  - Literacy and English as a Second Language (Box 47)
  - Literacy Instruction (Box 2)
  - Literacy Instruction (Box 69)
    See also Adult Literacy and Basic Skills Unit; Laubach Literacy International; Managing Adult Literacy Training; Libraries and Literacy Education
  - Literacy Review (Box 2)
  - Literacy Volunteers of America (Box 15)
  - Look Japan (Box 4)
  - Looking into (LRI) Leadership Courses (Box 1)
  - Love, Robert (Box 30)
  - Lucis Trust (Box 4)
  - Malawi (Box 37)
  - Managing Adult Literacy Training (Box 67)
  - Martinique (Box 37)
  - Mass Media (Box 3)
  - Mass Media A.E. (Box 24)
  - Media and Adult Learning (Box 43)
  - Media Instruction: Extension Education through Television (Box 47)
  - Media: 2 Misc. Pamphlets (Box 31)
  - Memo (Box 43)
  - Mexico (Box 5)
  - Mexico (Box 37)
  - Michigan State University
    - Conferences, 1961; 1967,; 1969,; 1976 (Box 59)
    - Study Team Reports on Non-Formal Education (Box 46)
  - Middle East Review (Box 24)
  - Middle States Association (Box 24)
  - Midwest Focus (Box 24)
  - Migrants, education of (Box 51)
  - Miller, Donald (Box 30)
  - Mills, Henry (Box 30)
  - Minorities, education of (Box 39)
  - Minorities, education of (Box 49)
  - Mississippi Community Education Quarterly (Box 24)
  - Momentum (Box 24)
  - Mountain Plains Adult Education Newsletter (Box 43)
  - Mumma, Richard (Box 30)
  - Museums: An Overview of Museums and Continuing Education (Box 48)
  - NACAC (Box 25)
  - NACAC Bulletin (Box 43)
  - NALPS (Box 25)
  - NAPCAE Exchange (Box 43)
  - National Adult Education Boards, Councils, etc. (Box 31)
  - National Advisory Council on Adult Education (Box 15)
  - National Advisory Council (Box 53)
  - National Asssociation of Secondary Schools' Principals (Box 51)
  - National Center for Education Brokering Newsletter (Box 43)
  - National Council for International Visitors (NCIV) (Box 43)
  - National Council for International Visitors (NCIV) (Box 25)
  - National Info Exchange (Box 25)
  - National Institute of Adult Continuing Education (NIACE) (Box 1)
  - National Institute of Adult Continuing Education (NIACE) (Box 25)
  - National Institute of Adult Education (Box 2)
  - National Report (Box 25)
  - National Report for Training and Development (Box 43)
  - National Report on Human Resources (Box 43)
  - National Training Laboratories, National Education Association (Box 2)
  - National University Continuing Education Association (NUCEA) (Box 13)
  - National University Continuing Education Association (NUCEA) Continuing Education News (Box 43)
  - National University Continuing Education Association (NUCEA) Newsletter (Box 43)
  - National University Extension Association (NUEA) (Box 15)
  - NATTS Network (Box 25)
  - NATTS News (Box 43)
  - NCEA (Box 1)
  - NEAP Newsletter (Box 43)
  - Netherlands (Box 37)
  - Network Circuit (Box 43)
  - Network Exchange (Box 43)
  - Network Fact Sheet (Box 43)
  - Network Vanguard (Box 43)
  - Neuffer, Frank (Box 30)
  - New Directions for University Adult Education (Box 1)
  - New York Association for Continuing Commmunity Education (Box 59)
  - New Zealand (Box 37)
  - New Zealand Journal of Adult Learning (Box 43)
  - News and Views (Box 25)
  - News and Views (Box 43)
  - News Education for Aging (Box 45)
  - News (Box 25)
  - Newsletters (Box 3)
  - Newsounds (Box 43)
  - Nexus (Box 1)
  - NFE Exchange (Box 43)
  - NHSC Bulletin (Box 1)
  - NHSC Bulletin (Box 43)
  - NHSC Misc. (Box 1)
  - NHSC News (Box 1)
  - NHSC News (Box 43)
  - NHSC Report (Box 1)
  - Niagara Falls Board of Education (Box 56)
  - Nigeria (Box 37)
  - NIJ Reports (Box 3)
  - NN+Q (Box 25)
  - Non-Governmental Universities and Colleges (Box 51)
    See also Agencies: Non-Governmental
  - Non-Formal Education Bulletin (Box 43)
  - Norway (Box 37)
  - Norwegian Institute of Adult Education Reports (Box 25)
  - Norwegian Institute of Adult Education Reports (Box 43)
  - Notes and Studies (Box 43)
  - Notes on the Commonwealth (Box 2)
  - NUEA, See National University Extension Association (NUEA)
  - NUFFIC-CESO Acquisition Lists (Box 67)
  - NYACCE (Box 43)
  - NYACCE (Box 49)
  - NYACCE (Box 71)
  - O'Brian, Doris (Box 30)
  - O'Neil, L.D. (Box 30)
  - O'Regan, William (Box 30)
  - Occupational and Continuing Education Newsletter (Box 20)
  - Occupational and Vocational Education (Box 70)
  - Occupational Programs (Box 69)
  - Odyssey (Box 20)
  - OERI Bulletin (Box 20)
  - Office of Economic Opportunity (Box 1)
  - Office on Education Credit and Credentials (Box 20)
  - Office on Education Credit and Credentials News (Box 43)
  - On Adult Learning (Box 20)
  - The Onondaga Citizens League, Reports 5 & 6 (Box 2)
  - Open Line (Box 20)
  - Open University Acquisition Lists (Box 66)
  - Opportunity Grants (Box 61)
  - Orbit (Box 44)
  - Orbit Organization Chart (Box 20)
  - Oregon State System of Higher Education (Box 62)
  - Organizational Papers, Misc. (Box 47)
  - Theory, Innovation, and Practice in Andragogy (Box 44)
  - PACE-Paragraphs About Continuing Education (Box 44)
  - Pachamama (Box 20)
  - Parenting Programs (Teenagers, Hyperactive Children) (Box 70)
  - Parkinson, George (Box 30)
  - Participatory Formation - A Network of the International Council for A.E. (Box 6)
  - Participatory Research Newsletter (Box 44)
  - Partnergram (Box 20)
  - Partners (Box 20)
  - Peace Corps (Box 28)
  - Peace Corps (Box 52)
  - Peace Newsletter (Box 44)
  - Pedagogical Reports (Box 65)
  - Personnalité Education Société (Box 30)
  - Philippines (Box 37)
  - Physical Education (Box 51)
  - Planned Parenthood World Population (Box 44)
  - PLUS (Box 6)
  - Poland (Box 37)
  - Population (Box 20)
  - Population Policy Compendium (Box 20)
    See also United Nations Population Policy Compendium
  - POPULI (Box 44)
  - Portugal (Box 37)
  - Posey, Roland B. (Box 30)
  - Problem Solving (Box 74)
  - Problem Solving (Box 74)
  - Professional (Box 70)
  - Professional Adult Educators (Box 70)
  - Professional Development (Box 31)
  - Professional Developments (Box 20)
  - Professors for Adult Education (Box 15)
    See also Commission of Professors of Adult Education (CPAE)
  - Program Development (Box 71)
  - Program Development (Box 72)
  - Programme News (Box 44)
  - Programs for Development (Box 71)
  - Programs for Women (Box 71)
  - Programs in Basic Education (Box 53)
  - Programs on Aging (Box 53)
  - Programs on Employment (Box 61)
  - Public Relations (Box 72)
  - Public Schools (Box 50)
  - Public Schools (Box 71)
  - Public Welfare (Box 32)
  - Publications from Universities (Box 6)
  - Publications on Adult Education Research, misc. (Box 74)
  - Pulse (Box 44)
  - Qatar (Box 37)
  - R&D for Higher Education (Box 44)
  - R+D Monthly Contracts (Box 20)
  - Re:ACE (Box 20)
  - Re:ACE Reader (Box 44)
  - The Reader (Box 20)
  - Readings in Program Development (Box 2)
  - Reals, Willis (Box 30)
  - Regents College Reports (Box 20)
  - Region Exchange (Box 1)
  - Region X: X Change (Box 44)
  - Release (Box 44)
  - Religion (Box 51)
  - Religion (Box 71)
  - Report of the Texas Literacy Council (Box 4)
  - Reports (Box 6)
  - Research in Adult Education: misc. pamphlets (Box 72)
  - Research in Adult Education: misc. pamphlets (Box 73)
  - Research in Adult Education: misc. pamphlets (Box 74)
  - Research in Distance Education (Box 20)
  - Residential Programs (Box 71)
  - Residential Short Courses (Box 1)
  - Resources in Migrant Education (Box 30)
  - Resources, print: Council of Europe, 3 volumes (Box 31)
  - Resources, print: misc. directories (Box 31)
    See also Directories
  - Resources, print: misc. (Box 31)
  - RLS Reporter (Box 3)
  - Romania (Box 37)
  - Russia, See U.S.S.R.
  - The Royal Bank Letter (Box 20)
  - Royce West (Box 30)
  - Scandinavian countries (Box 5)
  - Scotland (Box 5)
  - SCUTREA (Box 1)
  - SCUTREA (Box 67)
  - Second Thoughts (Box 44)
  - Selected bibliographies on Culture (Box 30)
  - SEVA-MANDIR Newsletter (Box 44)
  - Singapore (Box 37)
  - Society for the Advancement of Continuing Education for Ministry (SACEM) (Box 20)
    See also Continuing Educator (SACEM)
  - Software Consortium (Box 44)
  - Source (Box 7)
  - A Source Book for Education and Vocational Counselors: "The Alive Directory" (Box 67)
  - South Africa (Box 37)
    See also Africa
  - South End Press (Box 3)
  - The Spencer Foundation (Box 20)
  - Spencer Foundation (Box 44)
  - Spengler, Edwin, Brooklyn College (Box 30)
  - Spivey, Willis T. (Box 30)
  - Sri Lanka (Box 37)
  - Stamm, Fred (Box 30)
  - State Agencies (Box 48)
  - State Association Newsletter (Box 44)
  - State Education Department (Box 44)
  - State Education Leader (Box 44)
  - Statements and Speeches (Box 44)
  - Statements on Adult Education by Council of Europe, Germany, and Canada (Box 45)
  - Statistics (Box 65)
  - Studies in Continuing Education (Box 29)
  - Studies of Higher Education and Research (Box 20)
  - Studies of Higher Education and Research (Box 44)
  - Sudan (Box 37)
  - Sweden (Box 37)
  - Swedish National Board of Universities and Colleges (Box 44)
  - Swedish Research on Higher Education (Box 44)
  - Switzerland (Box 37)
  - Syracuse Scholar, vol. 8, Sp. 1987 (Box 30)
  - Syracuse University Publications (Box 15)
  - Syracuse University Publications in Continuing Education (SUPCE) (Box 4)
  - Syracuse University Publications in Continuing Education (SUPCE) (Box 15)
  - Syracuse University Publications in Continuing Education (SUPCE) (Box 26)
  - Tanzania (Box 37)
  - Teaching Adults (Box 44)
  - Teaching at a Distance (Box 44)
  - Techniques for Teaching Adults (Box 44)
  - Tel-Coms (Box 23)
  - Thailand (Box 5)
  - Thailand (Box 37)
  - Today (Box 23)
  - Training and Development (Box 67)
  - Training and Development at Syracuse University (Box 71)
  - Tranet (Box 23)
  - Transitions (Box 44)
  - Trends (Box 67)
  - Trends in Adult Education (Box 66)
  - Trinidad (Box 38)
  - Turkey (Box 38)
  - U.S. Agencies (Box 52)
  - U.S. Department of Health, Education, and Welfare (Box 56)
  - U.S. Department of Health, Education, and Welfare (Box 67)
  - U.S. Department of Health, Education, and Welfare Reports (Box 74)
  - U.S. Department of Labor (Box 1)
  - U.S. Professional Agencies (Box 50)
  - U.S.S.R. (Box 38)
  - Un Nuevo Dia (Box 44)
  - UNDP (Box 23)
  - UNDP (Box 67)
  - UNDP Misc. (Box 7)
  - UNESCO
    See also AEC UNESCO
    - UNESCO (Box 12)
    - UNESCO (Box 16)
    - UNESCO (Box 28)
    - UNESCO (Box 67)
    - UNESCO Adult Education (Box 44)
    - UNESCO Backgrounder (Box 45)
    - UNESCO Directions (Box 60)
    - UNESCO Educational Innovation and Information (Box 45)
    - UNESCO Facts and Figures (Box 45)
    - UNESCO Institute for Education Bibliography (Box 45)
    - UNESCO Regional AEC (Box 60)
    - UNESCO Surveys and Studies (Box 45)
    - UNESCO Unisist Newsletter (Box 45)
    - UNESCO-UNEP Environmental Education Newletter: CONNECT (Box 45)
  - The Unfinished Agenda (Box 1)
  - UNFPA Newsletter-Population (Box 23)
  - UNFPA Newsletter-Population (Box 45)
  - United Kingdom (Box 38)
  - United Nations (Box 3)
  - United Nations Population Policy Compendium (Box 44)
    See also Population Policy Compendium
  - United Nations University: International Centre for Distance Learning (Box 3)
  - United Nations University: International Centre for Education (Box 23)
  - United Nations University, "Work in Progress" (Box 23)
  - Universities Council for Adult Education (UCAE) (Box 1)
  - Universities Council for Adult Education (UCAE) and UCACE Annual Reports (Box 1)
  - University of British Columbia (Box 67)
  - University of Illinois at Urbana - Champaign Bulletin (Box 23)
  - University of Jamme (Box 23)
  - University of Liverpool Acquisition Lists (Box 66)
  - University of Nottingham (Box 1)
  - University of Reading Acquisition Lists (Box 67)
  - Unpublished International Occasional Papers in Adult Education (Box 32)
  - UNU Newsletter (Box 45)
  - UNU Work in Progress (Box 45)
  - Venezuela (Box 5)
  - Venezuela (Box 38)
  - Vient de Paraitre (Box 23)
  - Vocational Education (Box 23)
  - Vocational Education (Box 70)
    See also CEDEFOP Vocational Training Bulletin; European Bureau for Development of Vocational Training; European Centre for Development of Vocational Training; Occupational and Vocational Education; A Source Book for Education and Vocational Counselors: "The Alive Directory"; Vocational Training
  - Vocational Educator (Box 45)
  - Vocational Training (Box 45)
    See also Vocational Education
  - Voices for Peace (Box 45)
  - Voices Rising (Box 4)
  - Volunteer Voice (Box 45)
  - Vox Populi (Box 1)
  - Waters, John (Box 30)
  - West Africa Crier-Newsletter of the Subregion: AALAE (Box 45)
  - Who Press (Box 23)
  - Whole Non-Profit Catalog (Box 23)
  - Women - Education (Box 48)
    See also Center for Continuing Education of Women; Conference on Education and Occupational Needs of Asian-Pacific-American Women: National Institution of Education; ICAE: Women's Program Newsletter; Listen Real Loud-News of Women's Liberation Worldwide; Programs for Women; Worker's Education Association: WEA Women's Studies Newsletter
  - Women's World (Box 45)
  - Worker's Education Association (WEA)
    - Worker's Ed. Association (Box 51)
    - WEA News Journal of Workers Educational Association (Box 45)
    - WEA Women's Studies Newsletter (Box 45)
  - The World Bank (Box 3)
  - World Bank (Box 76)
  - World Development (Box 7)
  - World Education Report (Box 45)
  - World Education, Inc. (Box 3)
  - World Education, Inc. (Box 67)
  - World Goodwill (Box 23)
  - World Health (Box 7)
  - Worldlit Newsletter of World Literacy of Canada (Box 45)
  - Yugoslavia (Box 39)
  - Zambia (Box 39)
  - Zimbabwe (Box 39)
  - Miscellaneous
    - Various large pamphlets (Box 27)
    - Various Pamphlets (over 1/4 ") (Box 26)
    - Various Pamphlets (Box 26)
- Box listing
  - Council on the Continuing Education Unit - CCEU Reporter (Box 1)
  - CPAE Newsletter (Box 1)
  - The Unfinished Agenda (Box 1)
  - Universities Council for Adult Education (UCAE) and UCACE Annual Reports (Box 1)
  - Universities Council for Adult Education (UCAE) (Box 1)
  - NCEA (Box 1)
  - Vox Populi (Box 1)
  - NHSC Report (Box 1)
  - NHSC News (Box 1)
  - NHSC Bulletin (Box 1)
  - NHSC Misc. (Box 1)
  - Residential Short Courses (Box 1)
  - Looking into (LRI) Leadership Courses (Box 1)
  - New Directions for University Adult Education (Box 1)
  - Community Colleges; Misc. info (Box 1)
  - Office of Economic Opportunity (Box 1)
  - National Institute of Adult Continuing Education (NIACE) (Box 1)
  - U.S. Department of Labor (Box 1)
  - The IDRC Reports (Box 1)
  - University of Nottingham (Box 1)
  - The Continuing Educator (Box 1)
  - IFWEA-IVA-FIAET (Box 1)
  - FNV News (Box 1)
  - International Development Education Program, Univ. of Pittsburg (Box 1)
  - Region Exchange (Box 1)
  - Nexus (Box 1)
  - SCUTREA (Box 1)
  - International-Adult Education in Finland (Box 2)
  - International-Indice de Information (Box 2)
  - The Onondaga Citizens League, Reports 5 & 6 (Box 2)
  - Health Resource Center (Box 2)
  - Aries (Box 2)
  - AC, ACE (Box 2)
  - National Institute of Adult Education (Box 2)
  - Guides, Directories, Resources (Box 2)
  - Dissertations, Master Theses (Box 2)
  - Literacy Review (Box 2)
  - Literacy Instruction (Box 2)
  - National Training Laboratories, National Education Association (Box 2)
  - Community Development (Box 2)
  - Readings in Program Development (Box 2)
  - Adult Education Monograph, "Civil Defense for Adult..." (Box 2)
  - Notes on the Commonwealth (Box 2)
  - Continuing Education in Canada (Box 3)
  - Mass Media (Box 3)
  - BCEL (Box 3)
  - International-United Nations University: International Centre for Distance Learning (Box 3)
  - CRESST (Box 3)
  - World Education, Inc. (Box 3)
  - South End Press (Box 3)
  - RLS Reporter (Box 3)
  - COMBASE (Box 3)
  - NIJ Reports (Box 3)
  - International-United Nations (Box 3)
  - Christians and Israel (Box 3)
  - International-Commissions on Higher Education; "Letter" (Box 3)
  - Newsletters (Box 3)
  - CESO (Box 3)
  - AC/UNC Newsletter (Box 3)
  - Decade Watch (Box 3)
  - Literacy Documentation (Box 3)
  - The Free Press (Box 3)
  - The World Bank (Box 3)
  - Learning in New York (Box 4)
  - Cornell Cooperative Extension (Box 4)
  - Lucis Trust (Box 4)
  - Adult Education Association (AEA) Leadership Pamphlets (Box 4)
  - Adult Education Association (AEA) Leadership Digest (Box 4)
  - Adult Education Conference (Box 4)
  - ABE Staff and Conference (Box 4)
  - Syracuse University Publications in Continuing Education (SUPCE) (Box 4)
  - American Foundation for Continuing Education, Case Stories in American Politics (Box 4)
  - International Council for Correspondence Education (Box 4)
  - Report of the Texas Literacy Council (Box 4)
  - Adult Basic Education (ABE) National Teacher Training Study (Box 4)
  - Continuing Education in Africa (Box 4)
  - College of Agricultural and Life Sciences Quarterly (Box 4)
  - Look Japan (Box 4)
  - Voices Rising (Box 4)
  - Germany (Box 5)
  - AONTAS (Ireland) (Box 5)
  - Thailand (Box 5)
  - British Columbia (Box 5)
  - Korea (Box 5)
  - Australia (Box 5)
  - Holland (Box 5)
  - Scotland (Box 5)
  - Scandinavian countries (Box 5)
  - Venezuela (Box 5)
  - India (Box 5)
  - Europe (Box 5)
  - Bangladesh (Box 5)
  - Hungary (Box 5)
  - Jerusalem (Box 5)
  - France (Box 5)
  - England (Box 5)
  - Japan (Box 5)
  - Africa (Box 5)
  - China (Box 5)
  - Carribean (Box 5)
  - Iraq (Box 5)
  - Mexico (Box 5)
  - International-Indian Journal of A.E. (Box 6)
  - Reports (Box 6)
  - Education Policy Fellowship Program (Box 6)
  - PLUS (Box 6)
  - Publications from Universities (Box 6)
  - Participatory Formation - A Network of the International Council for A.E. (Box 6)
  - International Association Newsletter (Box 6)
  - International-Misc. (Box 6)
  - World Health (Box 7)
  - World Development (Box 7)
  - Choices (Box 7)
  - Cooperation South (Box 7)
  - Source (Box 7)
  - UNDP Misc. (Box 7)
  - Comparative Education Review (Box 7)
  - History of Education Quarterly (Box 7)
  - Convergence (Box 8)
  - Gewerkschaftliche Monatschefte (Box 9)
  - Adult Education and Development (Box 9)
  - Adult Education, A Journal of Research and Theory 1960-1982, 1956, 1957 (Box 10)
  - ERIC (Box 11)
  - UNESCO (Box 12)
  - IMPACT (Box 13)
  - National University Continuing Education Association (NUCEA) (Box 13)
  - Adult Education Research Conference (Box 14)
  - Aker, George (Box 14)
  - American Association for Adult Education (Box 14)
  - Association for Continuing Higher Education (Box 14)
  - Kellog (Box 15)
  - Laubach Literacy International (Box 15)
  - Library of Continuing Education at Syracuse University (Box 15)
  - Literacy Volunteers of America (Box 15)
  - National Advisory Council on Adult Education (Box 15)
  - National University Extension Association (NUEA) (Box 15)
  - Professors for Adult Education (Box 15)
  - Syracuse University Publications in Continuing Education (SUPCE) (Box 15)
  - SU Publications (Box 15)
  - UNESCO (Box 16)
  - AMT Events (Box 16)
  - Arbeits-und Sozialrecht be Luchterhand (Box 16)
  - ASPBAE Courier (Box 16)
  - Association for World Education Newsletter (Box 16)
  - Australian Journal of Adult Education (Box 16)
  - ATE Newsletter (Box 16)
  - Bank Street News (Box 16)
  - Basic Choices (Box 16)
  - BBC Continuing Education Newsletter (Box 16)
  - Incentives vs. Industry (Box 16)
  - Benchmark (Box 16)
  - British Open University Foundation (Box 16)
  - Canadian Journal of University Continuing Education (Box 16)
  - Capsules (Box 16)
  - Captrends (Box 16)
  - Carnegie Quarterly (Box 16)
  - CASAE/ACEEA Newsletter (Box 16)
  - Catalyst (Box 16)
  - CAUCE Bulletin (Box 16)
  - Council on the Continuing Education Unit - CCEU Reporter (Box 16)
  - CEDEFOP News (Box 16)
  - CEDEFOP Vocational Training Bulletin (Box 16)
  - Center for Continuing Education of Women (Box 16)
  - Centergram (Box 16)
  - CESO (Box 16)
  - Gewerkschaftliche Monatschefte (Box 17)
  - Growing Edge (Box 17)
  - Higher Education Research Report (Box 17)
  - Higher Education and National Affairs (Box 17)
  - Historical Foundations of A.E. (Box 17)
  - ICAE Women's Program Newsletter (Box 17)
  - ICAE Education and Criminal Justice Programme Newsletter (Box 17)
  - ICAE News (Box 17)
  - ICAE Participatory Formation Newsletter (Box 17)
  - ICAE Voices Rising (Box 17)
  - ICED Newsletter (Box 17)
  - IDRC Reports (Box 17)
  - ILO Information (Box 17)
  - ILSCAE Newsletter (Box 17)
  - Indian Educator (Box 17)
  - Ideas and Action (Box 17)
  - Ideas for Action (Box 17)
  - Indian Journal for A.E. (Box 17)
  - Indian Journal of A.E. (Box 17)
  - Innotech Newsletter (Box 17)
  - INSERVICE (Box 17)
  - Interdependent (Box 17)
  - Association of University Evening Colleges (AUEC) (Box 18)
  - Canadian Adult Education (Box 18)
  - Center for the Study of Liberal Education for Adults (CSLEA) (Box 18)
  - Coalition of Adult Education Organizations (CAEO) (Box 18)
  - Education in Europe (Box 18)
  - D.K. Agencies (Box 19)
  - Draper Fund Report (Box 19)
  - Earth Watch (Box 19)
  - Education for Aging (Box 19)
  - Education Exchange (Box 19)
  - Educational Innovation (Box 19)
  - Education and Training Programmes for Info Personnel (Box 19)
  - Educational News (Box 19)
  - Educational Record (Box 19)
  - En Toutes Lettres (Box 19)
  - FACS (Box 19)
  - Faits Noureaux (Box 19)
  - FNV (Box 19)
  - The Ford Foundation (Box 19)
  - For the Record (Box 19)
  - Forumarbeit (Box 19)
  - Georgia Center Quarterly (Box 19)
  - The Growing Edge (Box 19)
  - Highlights (Box 19)
  - Ideas and Action (Box 19)
  - ILO Publications (Box 19)
  - ILSS (Box 19)
  - Innotech (Box 19)
  - Innovation (Box 19)
  - Instructional Television News (Box 19)
  - International Association of Universities of the Third Age Newsletter (Box 19)
  - International Institute for the Unification of Private Law News Bulletin (Box 19)
  - International Literacy Year (Box 19)
  - International Network for Comparative... (Box 19)
  - International University Consortium (Box 19)
  - Occupational and Continuing Education Newsletter (Box 20)
  - Odyssey (Box 20)
  - Office on Education Credit and Credentials (Box 20)
  - OERI Bulletin (Box 20)
  - On Adult Learning (Box 20)
  - Open Line (Box 20)
  - The Orbit Organization Chart (Box 20)
  - Pachamama (Box 20)
  - Partnergram (Box 20)
  - Partners (Box 20)
  - Population (Box 20)
  - Population Policy Compendium (Box 20)
  - Professional Developments (Box 20)
  - Re:ACE (Box 20)
  - The Reader (Box 20)
  - Research in Distance Education (Box 20)
  - R+D Monthly Contracts (Box 20)
  - Regents College Reports (Box 20)
  - The Royal Bank Letter (Box 20)
  - Society for the Advancement of Continuing Education for Ministry (SACEM) (Box 20)
  - The Spencer Foundation (Box 20)
  - Studies of Higher Education and Research (Box 20)
  - CAEL (Box 21)
  - Coalition of Adult Education Organizations (CAEO) (Box 21)
  - CAETA (Box 21)
  - Campus Market Report (Box 21)
  - Capsule Report (Box 21)
  - Career Training (Box 21)
  - Carnegie Quarterly (Box 21)
  - CEC News (Box 21)
  - CEDEFOP (Box 21)